Now why do we call gas as sister
because it is a don't talk thing
and sometimes she caresses you lovingly and you get well, the
good news of the hospital
starts from them
that a girl is born and if there is a lot of noise in the hospital then their one word is
louder than everything, no matter how
deep the pain is, they apply ointment
and tell me one thing, even our doctors who are called God are
incomplete without them,
after taking care of their own people, everyone keeps this
promise to me of taking care of everyone as their own, only nursing keeps the promise,
ICICI Lombard wishes for the first
time in history questions on